In 1942 over 100,000 Americans were interned in prison camps. In America.
Come See the Paradise is a drama, romance, history film directed by Alan Parker.
In this drama from director Alan Parker, on-the-lam Jack McGurn flees to Los Angeles and takes
a job as a projectionist at a movie theater owned by a Japanese-American man.
Jack falls for the owner's daughter, Lily, but they are forced to elope
to Seattle when her father forbids the relationship.
The couple marry and have a daughter, but when World War II breaks out,
Jack is powerless to stop his new family's forced internment.
Jack McGurn, played by Dennis Quaid.
Lily Kawamura, played by Tamlyn Tomita.
Mr. Kawamura, played by Sab Shimono.
Frankie Kawamura, played by Brady Tsurutani.
Mrs. Kawamura, played by Shizuko Hoshi.
Charlie Kawamura, played by Stan Egi.
Come See the Paradise is a 1990 American historical drama film written and
directed by Alan Parker, and starring Dennis Quaid and Tamlyn Tomita.
Set before and during World War II, the film depicts the treatment of Japanese Americans in the United States following the
attack on Pearl Harbor, and the subsequent loss of civil liberties within the framework of a love story.
The film explores themes of new york city, world war ii,
forbidden love, love, interracial marriage.
The tone is emotional.